HENRY MOULE

hen10@hotmail.co.uk

U

07577635916

ł

https://moulie415.github.io/portfolio

noulie415

EXPERIENCE

Zenobē

Software Engineer | Since October 2023

I've made significant contributions across various projects during my time at Zenobē. On the Grid services optimization front, I've demonstrated expertise in technologies like Next.js, Node.js, and DynamoDB. Meanwhile, in the Electric Vehicle sector, I've leveraged Angular, NestJS, and PostgreSQL. Additionally, I've worked with Infrastructure as Code (IAC) practices utilizing Terraform and CDK.

SALT

Full Stack Engineer | Aug 2021 - Oct 2023

I work for the dating app SALT, as one of two developers, across the MERN (Mongo, Express, React/React Native, Node.js) stack. My focus is on the frontend, primarily on the React Native mobile app, but I do extensive work developing the Node.js backend, internal admin panel (React) and have completely rebuilt the website using Next.js, which I am also solely responsible for maintaining and keeping updated.

CarePlanner Ltd

JavaScript Developer | Nov 2019 - Aug 2021

At Careplanner, I worked on the then newest iteration of the mobile app, which provided an appointment rostering functionality that enabled carers to check in and out of appointments. The app uses React Native and consumes a GraphQL API, provided by AWS AppSync, which links it to the CarePlanner REST API.

Active Inspiration Technologies

Software Developer | January 2018 - November 2019

For Active Inspiration, I worked on the Fuell React Native app, however I also worked across the stack, developing the Fuell backend using Node.js/Parse Server. Active Inspiration had many clients for whom I developed various solutions, using technologies including React, Node.js, GraphQL and Next.js.

DYRNAN Communications

Junior Software Developer | July 2017 - December 2017

At DYRNAN, I worked mostly on the frontend, using React Native to develop an encrypted messaging app called Secoti (formerly Dyrnan).

Candour Creative

Freelance Web Developer | July 2016 - September 2016

Candour Creative outsourced some of their development work to me, which involved developing the website nicksweeney.co.uk using WordPress as a platform to create a custom CMS (PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, CSS).

WebCurl Ltd

Support Representative | November 2014 - June 2016

For my year in industry during my Computer Science degree, I worked for WebCurl, a web development agency based in Oxford, where I helped develop websites using Drupal (PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, CSS).

EDUCATION

A 4-year course (including a year in industry) covering Java with a focus on OOP and other modules, including Python, C/C++, JavaScript and C#. My course also involved a teaching module, for which I spent a week as a teaching assistant, helping to teach Python and Scratch at a secondary school. In my final year, as part of my final year project, I developed a maths game called Equation Dragger, that is currently available on the Google Play Store.

Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) Computer Science at Oxford Brookes University | 2013 - 2017

A-levels: Mathematics (B), Music Technology (C), Religious Studies (C), GCSEs: 10 GCSEs including an A* in music and A grades in Maths, History, Biology, Chemistry, Physics and Religious Studies.

Queen Elizabeth's Hospital | 2006 - 2013

SKILLS

I have also worked in multiple Agile environments, with experience working with Jira, Asana and Hive.

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- React Native
- React.js
- Node.js

- GraphQL
- Next.is
- MongoDB
- C#
- Unity

- Git
- jQuery
- Swift
- Objective-C
- Kotlin

About me

I am an experienced full stack developer who has been working primarily with React/React Native on the frontend since 2017 and Node.js on the backend since 2018. My colleagues have described me as efficient, dependable and willing to go the extra mile. Outside of work you'll find me working on various coding projects. I am currently working with a Personal Trainer and Osteopath who commissioned me to develop a fitness/workout app. I also love playing the guitar and enjoy helping out with the worship team